charlotterusse.com 2019-01-05

# Privacy Policy | Charlotte Russe

**Last Updated June 20, 2014:**

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Charlotte Russe values our customers and respects your privacy. This privacy policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use and protect it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. By providing your personal information to Charlotte Russe, you are consenting to the manner in which we collect, use, disclose, protect and otherwise manage that information. 

If our information practices change, we will post an updated version of the policy on our website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the “Last Updated” date that appears above and that will be the date on which the new policy becomes effective. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our website and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. Your continued use of our website constitutes your consent to be bound by the revised policy. 

You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy at any time. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us as described in the section below entitled, "How do I contact you?"

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

#### What kind of personal information does Charlotte Russe collect?

We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, or credit card number when you visit our website or one of our stores, place an order online or by phone, make an in-store purchase, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online or by phone and in our stores. We may combine all of this information with information about you that we acquire from our joint marketing partners and from unrelated third parties. 

We allow you to register and log into Charlotte Russe and connect your Charlotte Russe account to your social media account. If you elect to connect your social media account to your Charlotte Russe account, certain information will be shared by your social media account with Charlotte Russe such as your name, gender, profile picture, list of friends, your profile, likes and data that is part of your profile or your friends? profiles. When you connect your Charlotte Russe account to a social media account, you are authorizing Charlotte Russe to collect, store, and use any and all social media information and content we receive from your social media account in accordance with this Privacy Policy. For information about the information that Charlotte Russe shares with the social medial account, please see “Does Charlotte Russe share my personal information?” 

#### How does Charlotte Russe use my personal information?

We may use your personal information in the following ways: 

  * To process and fulfill your order, including sending you emails to confirm your order status and shipment
  * To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications
  * To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions
  * To help us learn more about your shopping preferences
  * To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services
  * To enhance your shopping experience in our stores, through our catalog or online
  * To analyze trends and statistics
  * To protect the security or integrity of our website and our business
  * To contact you if necessary
  * To facilitate social sharing functionality

#### Does Charlotte Russe share my personal information?

We may share your personal information in the following ways: 

  * We may share your information with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use or disclosure of your information.
  * We may share your information when we team up with another company to jointly offer or provide products, services, contests, or promotions to our customers.
  * We may share your information to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of Charlotte Russe or others.

In addition, if you choose to participate in any third-party scrip, loyalty, or similar program in which a Charlotte Russe brand is a participating vendor, and you authorize Charlotte Russe or our credit card processor to provide information about your purchases to the organization administering the program, we will share your personal information with that program. 

In the unlikely event of a sale or merger of Charlotte Russe or any of our businesses, assets or brands, our customers' personal information and other information we have collected as described in this policy may be among the transferred business assets. 

If you connect your social media account and your Charlotte Russe account, we will share your social media user name, picture, and likes, as well as your shopping activities and comments with other website visitors and with your friends associated with your social media account. We will also share the same information with your social media account provider. By connecting your Charlotte Russe account and your social media account you are authorizing Charlotte Russe to share information with your social media account provider and you understand that the use of the shared information will be governed by the social media site?s privacy policy. If you do not want your personal information shared with other users or with your social media account provider, please do not connect your social media account with your Charlotte Russe account and do not participate in social sharing on our website. 

#### How do I access or change my personal information?

You can review and change certain personal information related to your use of our online website (such as your name and contact information). To access your information at a Charlotte Russe website, simply sign in to your account using your email address and password, and you will be able to edit your personal information in your account profile. 

You can also ask us to update your personal information by contacting us as described in the section below entitled, "How do I contact you?" Please note that any request to update your personal information may take up to 10 days for your email request and 6-8 weeks for your postal mail request. 

#### How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?

Charlotte Russe wants to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information, such as information about special offers and sales events, from one or more of our brands, you can let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the section below entitled, "How do I contact you?"

Please be sure to include your full name and the email address you used when you registered with or made a purchase from the Charlotte Russe brand. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Charlotte Russe. If you change your mind, you can start receiving promotional communications from us again by logging into your online account and changing your preferences, by signing up when you visit our website or our stores or when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, or by contacting customer service. 

Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order. 

#### How does Charlotte Russe protect kids' privacy?

Charlotte Russe is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request or collect personal information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our website is a general audience site and is not targeted to or intended for use by children. If you are a parent and believe we may have inadvertently collected such information from your child, please notify us immediately by sending an e-mail to [customerservicecr@charlotterusse.com](mailto:customerservicecr@charlotterusse.com)  
or phoning us toll free at 1-888-211-7271. 

#### Third Party Ads

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Please note that these companies may use information about your visit to this website and third-party websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this website, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices with respect to it, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. 

## OTHER INFORMATION

#### Other Information We Collect

“Other Information” is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as browser information, information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies, demographic information and other information provided by you or aggregated information. 

#### How Does Charlotte Russe Collect Other Information?

We and our third party service providers may collect Other Information through your browser: Certain information is collected by most browsers, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system version and Internet browser type and version. We use this information to ensure that our website functions properly. 

When you visit the Charlotte Russe website, we collect information to improve the content of our website for marketing and promotional purposes. Each time you visit our website, our web server automatically recognizes your IP address, monitor resolution and what type of browser you are using. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and collect customer information gathered in the course of joining our online member base and/or processing sales transactions. 

#### How does Charlotte Russe use cookies?

We use "cookies," which are small data files that are stored on your computer?s hard drive when you visit a website. Cookies enable you to shop on our website and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience. 

For example, we may use cookies to enable you to use certain website features, remember the items in your shopping cart, store your preferences, recognize you when you return to our website, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your use of our website. Cookies may also be used to collect transaction information needed by a scrip or loyalty program to which you have authorized us to provide your personal information. (See the section above entitled, "Does Charlotte Russe share my information?") 

You can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, then please call us on 1-888-211-7271 to place your order. 

#### How does Charlotte Russe use pixel tags?

We use "pixel tags" (also called "web beacons" or "clear gifs"), which are tiny graphic images, on our website and in our emails. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers' online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our website and our advertising. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information. 

Pixel tags on our website may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the website. This information may include your computer's Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also collect information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to our website. Because we do not track our website users over time and across third-party websites, we do not respond to browser do-not-track signals. 

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us. 

We also work with third-party companies that use tracking technologies to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our website and third-party websites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications. Please see our section on “Third Party Ads” for more information. 

Information such as your gender, birthday, zip code, as well as other information, such as your preferred means of communication, is collected when you voluntarily provide this information. Unless combined with personal information, this information does not personally identify you or any other user of the site. 

Aggregated personal information does not personally identify you or any other user of the site, (for example, we may aggregated personal information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code). 

#### How We Use and Disclose Other Information?

Please note that we may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as personal information under applicable law, then we may use and disclose Other Information for all the purposes for which we use and disclose personal information. 

In some instances, we may combine Other Information with personal information (such as combining your name with your birthday or likes or combining information collected from cookies with your personal information). If we combine any Other Information with personal information, the combined information will be treated by us as personal information as long as it is combined.

## IMPORTANT INFORMATION

#### What is "phishing"?

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information such as your user name or password, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information through email. 

#### What about links to other websites?

For your convenience and information, our website may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our website. 

#### How do I know my personal information is secure?

We take precautions, including the use of encryption technologies and authentication tools, to protect the security of your personal information and to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information. 

When you enter your personal information on our website, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https." 

If for any reason you cannot access the secure server, or if you're not quite comfortable shopping online at our website, please feel free to place your order with us by telephone at the number listed in the section below entitled,"How do I contact you?" 

Some browsers and firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you will be unable to connect to our server so you will not have to worry about mistakenly placing an order through an unsecured connection. If you can't access the server, you can place your order by calling our Customer Service Representatives at 1-888-211-7271. 

#### How do I contact you?

For questions about our privacy policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, to update your personal information, or to place an order, you can contact Charlotte Russe by email, telephone, or postal mail: 

Charlotte Russe, Inc.  
5910 Pacific Center Blvd. Suite 120  
San Diego, CA 92121  
1-888-211-7271
